人人影视
YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译：Iz    红豆包    奈奈良
校对：Iz          总监   IZ
时间轴：今        后期：吉吉
《开心汉堡店》
第三季第十五集
有没有注意到我有什么不同
Anyone notice anything different about me?
-新咪咪  -新态度
- New boobs? - New 'tude?
错  大错特错  我怀孕了
Wrong and wronger. I'm pregnant!
啥
Wha...?
我们要在生理卫生课上学习照顾面粉宝宝
We're getting flour sack babies in health class.
你的确是面色红润
You do have that glow.
我的宝贝要有小宝贝了
Aw, my little baby's having babies.
我成性感外婆了
I'm a sexy grandma.
真不敢相信他们居然让你来照顾一个孩子
I can't believe they're going to let you be in charge of a child.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
我生来就是当妈的料
I was born to be a mother.
我会从屁股拉一袋面粉出来
I'm gonna pull a flour sack out of my bottom.
大家早上好
Morning, everyone.
唐・德雷柏这一季貌似发福了啊
Wow, Don Draper's kind of fat this season.
唐・德雷柏:美剧《广告狂人》的主人公
你穿这身可真潇洒  先生
Ooh, you look sharp, mister.
陪审团会以
The jury is gonna find
"太英俊罪"起诉你的
you guilty of handsome in the first degree.
我是去为停车罚单申诉  琳
I'm contesting a parking ticket, Lin.
没什么陪审团
There isn't a jury.
这西装帅成这样  这罪名你是逃不掉了
You've got a suit that won't acquit.
等一下  你这身没污渍
Wait a second, there's no stains on that.
这不是你的西装
That's not your suit.
我那套穿不下了  这是我问莫特借的
My suit didn't fit anymore, so I borrowed this from Mort.
某个倒霉鬼的老婆为葬礼带了两套西服
Some poor guy's wife brought two
把这套给忘那儿了
for the burial and left this one behind.
我怎么就没遇上穿死人衣服的好事儿
Why don't I ever get to wear dead people's clothes?
我死后会把我的袜子都留给你
When I'm gone, I'll leave you all my socks.
人家想要的
Aw, I wanted those.
好了  现在大家都有各自的生活伴侣了
Okay, class, now that you've been assigned life partners,
准备告别童年  迎接你们的宝宝吧
kiss your childhood good-bye and your babies hello.
所有的父亲们都到前面来
Let's have all the fathers come up
承担你们一时冲动的后果吧
and assume responsibility for their reckless behavior.
崔维斯・奥尔布赖特
Travis Albright.
他眼睛长得像你
He has your eyes.
但愿没遗传到你的注意力紊乱多动症
But hopefully not your A.D.D.
吉恩・贝尔彻
Gene Belcher.
他真美
He's beautiful.
现在要记住  即使是最小的错误
Now, remember, even the smallest mistake
也会影响你宝贝的一生
will affect your child's life forever.
天哪
Oh, my God!
抱歉  我能再要一个吗
I'm sorry. Can I have another one?
我可不敢说  吉恩
I don't know, Gene.
婴儿是能说要就要的吗
Can people just have another baby?
是的  的确可以  给你吧
Well, yes, they can. So here you go.
但如果你再失手  我就让你不及格
But if you drop this one, I'll have to fail you.
吉恩  你这门课F得定了
Gene, you're getting an F.
F代表"失败的父亲"
For "Failing father."
"失败"的英文"fail"以"F"开头
我可以还原的
I can fix this!
看  他好了
See, he's fine.
他没事  他很快乐
He's good; He's happy.
我要一个宝宝
Ah! I need a baby!
回到你的座位上去  吉恩
Go back to your seat, Gene.
把你脸上的"宝宝"给我擦干净了
And wipe that baby off your face.
法院
我没看到停车收费器
I couldn't see the meter
因为有个小孩儿站前面把它挡住了
because there was a kid standing in front of it, and, um,
他长得刚好和收费器一般高
he was exactly meter-sized.
-真的吗  -没错
- Really? - Yeah.
和收费器一般高
Meter-sized?
我想他是在那边闲逛  法官
Well, and-and I think he was loitering, sir.
贝尔彻先生
Well, Mr. Belcher...
这次就放你一马
...we're gonna let this one go.
-真的吗  -是的
- Really? - Yes.
-我会撤消这个罚单  -好吧
- I'm dismissing the ticket. - Okay, wow.
下次雇个泊车小弟
Maybe next time use the valet, huh?
我会的
I will.
我一定会的
I definitely will...
下一个案子
Next case!
你看着像是个有地位的人
You look important.
-你能娶了我妈妈吗  -啥
- Will you marry my mom? - What? Uh, oh, um...
亲爱的  别去烦那位体面的绅士
Sweetie, sweetie, don't bother that nice gentleman.
真抱歉
I'm so sorry.
傻孩子
He's an idiot.
没关系的
Ah, I'm sure.
"绅士"  哇塞
"Gentleman." Wow.
我一定会是个好爸爸
I would've been a great dad.
吉恩  振作些
Gene, cheer up.
为何不把精力放在产后恢复身材上面呢
Why not focus your energy on losing that baby weight?
不  我正产后忧郁呢
No! I'm moping.
我要绕道回家
I'm gonna take the long way home.
告诉老妈晚餐别做任何和面粉有关的东西
Tell Mom not to make anything for dinner with flour.
甜点的巧克力蛋糕也不许加面粉
And a flour-less chocolate cake for dessert!
什么东西
What was that?
-你好  -谁在说话
- Hello. - Who said that?
-你好  -你是鬼吗
- Hello. - Are you a ghost?
我可是捉妖师  同时还是名警官
'Cause I'm a Ghostbuster! And I'm a police officer.
我还是射手座的
And a Sagittarius.
我不明白你的指令
I do not understand your command.
请坐下来建立个人档案
Please sit to create profile.
现在请说出你的名字
Please log in with name now.
-吉恩  -你好  吉恩
- Gene. - Hello, Gene.
请坐下来建立个人档案
Please sit to create profile.
好吧  但是不要耍花招
Okay, but don't try anything funny.
请求启动幽默功能
Request for funny activated.
正在载入笑话
Loading joke.
你会讲笑话
You know jokes?
咚咚
Knock-knock.
英语中的"敲门笑话"
是谁呀
Who's there?
马彤
Botany.
马彤怎么了
Botany who?
最近有买什么好的马桶吗
Bot-any good toilets lately?
-我懂了  -你喜欢吗
- I get it! - Did you like that?
我有上百万个笑话呢
I have a million of them.
一百一十万零五个笑话
1,100,005.
你真酷
You are so cool.
一词多义  "cool"同时有"酷"和"冷却"的意思
启动座圈降温功能
Cooling seat now.
不  不  帮我暖暖
No, no, warm it up.
我喜欢屁股暖暖的[我爱吃烤热的面包]
I like my buns toasted.
一词多义  "bun"有"面包"和"屁股"的意思
预热座圈中
Warming seat now.
英国女王是谁
Who's the Queen of England?
伊丽莎白二世
Elizabeth the second.
-谁是黑夜女王  -惠特尼・休斯顿
- Who's the Queen of the Night? - Whitney Houston.
《黑夜女王》是惠特尼・休斯顿演唱的歌曲
谁是...  等等
Who's the Queen of the... wait a second!
坐浴盆  别介意我按这个
Bidet? Don't mind if I bid-do.
我就知道会是这样  但我就是想按
I knew that would happen, but I did it anyway.
我不想以朋友的身份拍你马屁
I'm not just saying this because I'm your friend,
但这也太神奇了
but that is amazing.
警报
Alert.
水箱水位低
Auxiliary water tank low.
请主用户维修
I require maintenance from primary user.
"主用户"
"Primary user"?
我以前从没想过要一个属于自己的马桶
Wow, I've never cared for a toilet of my own before.
生活总是让人措手不及
I guess you're never really ready.
喝吧  孩子
There you go, thirsty boy.
多谢  吉恩
Thank you, Gene.
启动夜间照明灯
Activating night light.
已经是晚上了吗
Uh-oh, it's night already?
我得回家了
I better go home.
我要回去和我的姐妹们打赌
I'm gonna bet my sisters $1,000
一千块赌树林里有个会说话的马桶
that there isn't a talking toilet in the woods.
我管这叫得来全不费工夫
That's what I call easy money.
播放埃迪・莫尼的歌曲
Playing artist Eddie Money.
美国70-80年代音乐家
不不  取消  撤消
No, no, cancel! Undo!
取消播放埃迪・莫尼
Cancelling Eddie Money.
你还真听话
Wow, you really listen.
你真棒
You're the best.
好吧  回见
Okay, see ya.
再见  吉恩
Good-bye, Gene.
喂  小家伙
Hey, little man.
你吹口哨的这首歌是从哪儿听来的
Where'd you hear that song you're whistling?
这不是一首歌
It wasn't a song.
我在取笑一只鸟
I-I was making fun of a bird.
某只小鸟跟我透露
Well, a little bird told me
你也许看见了我正在寻找的东西
you might have seen something I'm looking for:
一个马桶
A toilet.
我没见过
I haven't seen one.
我连用都没用过
I-I've never even used one!
-过来  一会儿就好  -不
- Come here, just for a sec. - Uh, no.
-我有话要说  -好  你用吼的吧
- I want to tell you something. - Ma... okay. Yell it.
我是说  我有东西给你
I mean, I mean, I want to give you something.
我什么都不缺
I already have enough.
你又不知道我要给你什么
You don't know what it is.
我知道  我只是感觉我拿不了你那东西
I know. I just feel like I know what I can carry
我晚上还有事
and I have my... night planned.
你中彩票了
You won the lottery.
-那我最好赶紧去辞职  -在哪儿
- Then I better go quit my job! - Where is it?!
我的马桶在哪儿
Where's my toilet?!
你好  我叫小宝贝贝尔彻
你现在是我的小宝贝了  贝尔彻
You're my baby boy now, Belcher.
我好像感觉大家因为这套西装
I'm not sure, but I think people are
对我的态度也不同了
treating me different because of this suit.
昨晚在大街上  一个流浪汉还向我敬礼
Last night on the street, this homeless guy saluted me.
真不敢相信我差点埋了那套西服
Can't believe I almost buried that suit.
现在你就算埋了它也会从坟墓里爬出来
If you buried it now, it'd probably claw itself out of the grave
回到鲍鲍身上
to get back on Bobby.
这都能拍成一部很棒的电影了
That would make a great movie.
西服墓地
Suit Cemetery.
我会看的  但只看日场
I'd see that, but only the matinee.
我可不想回家面对阴森森的房间
I wouldn't want to come home to a dark closet.
-三件套来了  -我
- Ooh, here comes the three-piece! - Ah, I...
领结  当心
Bow tie, oh, look out!
-它抓到我了  -琳达  求你别演了
- Oh, it got me! - Linda, please.
-我以后还想在这儿吃饭呢  -我死了
- I don't want to find another place to eat. - I'm dead.
打扰了  请问知道曼斯特酒吧在哪儿吗
Excuse me, do you know where Maestro's Bistro is?
抱歉  不知道  我
Sorry, no, I...
-这家餐馆怎么样  -不知道呢
- What about this place? - Hmm, I don't know.
-这里的食物怎么样  -很不错
- How's the food here? - Uh, it's really good.
我每天都来这里吃饭
I eat here every day.
他都觉得好吃呢
If it's good enough for him.
反正我也是一个人  也许我该加入你们
Well, uh, since I'm dining alone, maybe I'll join you.
你一个人  这怎么可能
You dining alone? How does that happen?
女士们
Whoa, whoa, ladies!
矜持点
Bring it down a notch, huh?
我还是在后面给你们找一处好座位吧
Why don't I get you a nice booth in the back, right?
我们都曾单身过
We were all single once,
但也没必要就当荡妇  好吗
but you don't got to be a slut about it, you know?
地方有点远  但很神奇
It's just a little bit further, and it's amazing!
是尸体吗  像电影《伴我同行》里那样
Is it a body, like in Stand By Me?
或是一位出色的数学老师
Or a great math teacher,
像电影《为人师表》里那样
like in Stand and Deliver?
现在为您呈现  看
I present to you, voila!
你好  吉恩
Hello, Gene.
这什么玩意
What the hell?
探知到新用户
New user detected.
请说出您的姓名  以创建个人档案
Please say your name to create profile.
我滴妈呀
Holy crap!
你好  我滴妈呀
Hello, Holy Crap.
你好
Hi.
看见了吧  这就是我的马桶朋友
And boom, my friend the toilet.
说"宝宝盘"[一道美国式中国菜]
Say "Pupu platter."
宝宝盘
Pupu platter.
-说"核香肠"  -核香肠
- Say "Nuclear wiener." - Nuclear wiener.
-说"下丘脑"  -下丘脑
- Say "Hypothalamus." - Hypothalamus.
说"我爱你  蒂娜"
Say "I love you, Tina."
我爱你  蒂娜
I love you, Tina.
说"我爱你  蒂娜
Say "I love you, Tina.
我不是马桶  是个男生"
I'm not a toilet, I'm a boy."
-不要  -好吧
- No. - Oh.
警告 水箱水位低
Alert. Auxiliary water tank low.
请补水
Please fill.
好咧  吃饭时间到
Okay, time for din-din.
你干脆喂它母乳得了  吉恩
Why don't you just breast-feed it, Gene?
我倒是想呢
I tried.
可它只喝瓶装水
This one only takes a bottle.
谢谢你
Thank you.
维护完毕
Maintenance complete.
你跟它处得真融洽  吉恩
You're really great with him, Gene.
因为他是个好马桶啊
He's just a really good toilet.
警告
Alert.
电池电量剩余3小时
Three hours of battery life remaining.
请连接电源
Please connect to a power source.
电源
Power source?
什么电源
What power source?
我需要220伏特的专用漏电保护器
I require a dedicated 220 volt ground fault circuit interrupter.
别担心  我们会带你离开这儿
Don't worry, we'll get you out of here.
肾上腺素  到你表现的时候了
Adrenaline, do your thing!
吉恩  冷静下
Gene, calm down.
为会说话的马桶找电源这种事
You're not the first person who's had to find
你绝对不是第一个
a power source for his talking toilet.
没错  我们这就回家
Right, right. We'll have to go home
弄些电池  电源线
and get some batteries, extension cords.
再偷辆车  把汽油抽到发电机里
We'll steal a car, we'll siphon the gasoline into a generator.
我们会帮你的  吉恩
We'll help you, Gene.
谢谢  蒂
Thanks, T.
给马桶充电可是个大工程
It takes a village to charge a toilet.
你们这些小鬼去哪儿了
Where have you kids been?
-这么晚了  -合唱团
- It's late. - Glee club.
-私人俱乐部  -滑雪俱乐部
- Key club. - Ski club?
参加课外活动啊  我喜欢
Oh, extracurriculars. I love it.
我们仨的俱乐部出了点紧急状况
Yeah, we have a triple-club emergency.
需要大量的电源线
We need extension cords and lots of them.
啧啧啧  这不是"小宝贝贝尔彻"吗
Well, well, well, if it isn't Baby Boy Belcher.
你是不是把这丢哪儿了
Did you lose this somewhere?
孩子们  这人正在找他丢失的马桶
Uh, kids, this guy's looking for a lost toilet.
另外他脑子没问题
And he's not crazy.
他叫马克思  抱歉  我忘记你的姓了
He's Max, uh... sorry, I didn't, uh, catch your last name.
崇马彤
Eh, Flush.
你叫马克思・崇马彤  正在找一个马桶
Your name's Max Flush and you're looking for a toilet?
真有意思
That's funny.
他叫鲍勃・汉堡
And his name is Bob Burger.
什么
What?
他叫鲍勃・汉堡
His name is Bob Burger.
-才不是  -就是
- Um, it's not. - It is.
-不是  -不是吗
- It isn't, no. - It's not?
-不是  你认真的吗  -鲍勃・汉堡
- No. Are you serious? - Bob Burgers.
-怎么  -鲍勃・汉堡
- How... - Bob Burgers.
-那我想的这个人是谁  -我不知道
- Then who am I thinking of? - I don't know.
但  但餐馆明明就叫
But-but the sign.
各位  我这儿正找马桶呢
Okay, well, I'm still missing a toilet.
它在我运送的途中从车里掉了出来
I was delivering it, but it fell off my truck.
我的马桶值1万4千美元
My toilet's worth $14,000.
所以我一定要找到它
So I'm gonna find it.
1万4千美元
$14,000?
给我1万4块  让马桶拉我身上都行
For 14 grand, I'd let that toilet poop on me.
琳
Lin.
我的马桶很特别
My toilet's special.
是世界上最先进的
State of the art.
我愿不惜一切来找到它
I'm very motivated to find it.
你有告诉过马桶你的想法吗
Have you told the toilet how you feel?
我们心照不宣
The toilet knows how I feel!
崇马彤先生  我们看到它会通知您的
Okay, Mr. Flush, we'll-we'll let you know if we see it,
餐馆今天要提前关门  所以...
and, uh, we're closing early, so...
提前关门
Closing early?
对  我要用那张罚单省下的钱
Yeah, I'm gonna use the money I saved on that ticket
穿着这身衣服和琳达去吃顿大餐
and take Linda and my suit out to a nice dinner.
我们要去百福尔餐厅  可高级了
We're going to Beville's! It's fancy.
他们用篮子盛面包  里面还铺着纸巾
They give you bread in a basket with a napkin inside of it.
-能加我一个不  -不能
- Can I come? - No.
-好吧  -好了各位
- Oh. - Okey dokey.
看来我得先走了
I guess I'll just be on my way then.
走之前  我们得把垃圾扔出去
Before we go, we should take out the trash.
琳  你能去扔一下吗  我穿着正装呢
Lin, do you mind? I'm kind of in a suit.
好吧  不过别指望我躺平了
Okay, but I'm not gonna lie down
让你踩着我过水坑  先生
in any puddles for you to cross, mister.
开玩笑的  我会的
Just kidding, I will.
天哪  他没有走
Oh, no, he's not leaving!
他在监视我们
He's staking us out.
近期我们得低调点了
We'll have to lay low for a while.
不能低调  我们要把马桶带回来
We can't lay low. We have to get back to the toilet!
我们得制定个计划
We'll need a plan.
蒂娜  取消我所有预约
Tina, cancel all of my appointments.
那得花点工夫
That's gonna take a while.
吉恩  帮我挡下电话
Gene, hold my calls.
他要跟我换眼球
Now he wants to switch eyes!
好啦  营救马桶行动开始
Okay, operation Capture the Throne is go.
齐克和小吉米会在集结点跟我们会合
Zeke and Jimmy Jr. will meet us at the rally point.
安迪和奥利正往这儿赶
Andy and Ollie are on their way here.
大家都知道自己要做什么吧
Everybody know what they're doing?
你是指平时还是这次的计划里
In general or in the plan?
计划里  蒂娜
The plan, Tina.
我们要等老爸老妈走了才能行动
We just have to wait for Mom and Dad to get out of here, already.
马桶只剩两小时电量了
The toilet's only got two hours left.
我这身怎么样
How do I look?
没人会看你的  琳
Well, no one's gonna be looking at you, Lin.
-好吧  -拜
- Oh. - Bye!
-拜  -拜
- Bye. - Bye.
-拜  拜  拜  拜  -拜
- Bye, bye, bye, bye, bye. - Bye.
-拜拜  -拜
- Bye, bye. - Bye.
不许进我房间
Stay out of my room.
安迪和奥利来了
Here come Andy and Ollie.
他们怎么这么慢
What's taking them so long?
他们都想把对方抱起来
They're both trying to carry each other at the same time.
抱歉了  萨曼莎
Sorry, Samantha.
我是蒂娜
I'm Tina!
不  你是我
No, you're me.
我卖钢笔为我们海狸童子军筹款
I'm selling pens to benefit my Beaver Scout troop.
你要买几支
How many can I put you down for?
我不买
None.
-七支吗  -一支也不要
- Seven? - Zero.
-零百零七支吗  -好吧  我买两支
- Zero hundred and seven? - Oh, fine, I'll take two.
喂
Hey!
百福尔餐厅
二人浪漫约会
Party of two-ty-toot-toot.
我这人可有意思了  你一定会喜欢我的
I'm a fun customer; You're gonna love me.
抱歉  没有预约的话要等一个小时
I'm sorry, unless you have a reservation, it's an hour wait.
一小时  你说真的吗
An hour, really, hmm?
你们一起的吗
Oh, are you together?
也许还有空位  我查查
Maybe we have something. Let me check.
您需要鸡尾酒吗
May I bring you a cocktail?
我要苹果马提尼
Ooh, appletinis.
对  来两杯
Uh, yeah, we'll have two.
一人两杯
Two each.
我说真的
I'm serious.
我来了  马桶
I'm coming, toilet!
别离开我
Don't you quit on me!
我们现在可是一条船上的人了
Guess we're in the same boat now,
小宝贝贝尔彻
Baby Boy Belcher.
我的乖乖
Oh, my.
搞什么...
What the...?
去皇颅岛好好玩啊  笨蛋
Have a great time on King's Head Island, sucker!
租辆高尔夫球车吧  超好玩的
Rent a golf cart; They're super fun.
这事儿还没完
This isn't over!
我能让我的膝盖微笑
I can make my knees smile.
马桶
Toilet?
你好吉恩
Hello, Gene.
请求维护
Maintenance required.
别担心  马上就帮你
Don't worry, help is on the way.
电池电量剩余33分钟
33 minutes of battery life remaining.
会好起来的
Everything's going to be okay.
我们马上又能一起说笑话了
We'll be telling jokes again in no time.
载入笑话
Loading joke.
咚咚
Knock-knock.
是谁
Who's there?
爱插嘴的马桶
Interrupting toilet.
爱插嘴的马桶...
Interrupting toilet...?
坚持住  伙计
Hang in there, buddy.
我们马上修好你
We're going to get you fixed up.
这是那边的那对夫妻送的
These are from the couple over there.
谢谢你们
Thank you.
没你的份  都是给这位先生的
Ah... not for you, for him.
可我还没喝完
Oh, I still haven't finished
那位足部诊所医生送的"激情海岸"
my Sex on the Beach from that foot clinic doctor.
我们得加快速度
Yeah, we got to pick up the pace.
双管齐下  走一个
Double fist 'em... go.
这样行吗  琳
I don't know, Lin,
我开车来的呢 还是其实是你开的
I mean, I drove, or maybe you drove.
我们是开车来的  对吧
One of us drove, right?
没关系  我们可以叫猪猪车
It's all right, we-we'll take a snatchy.
啥
What?
我可以叫猪猪车
We'll take a snatchy.
猪猪车是什么玩意儿
What-What's a snatchy?
就是黄色的那个
The yellow thing.
再提示得更明白点
Well, I need a better hint than that.
-有轮子的  -出租车吗
- It's got wheels. - A taxi?
对  租租车
Yeah, a snacky.
-你刚才说的是...  -租租车
- You said... - Snacky!
等等  你老在变
Wait, you keep changing it.
你懂就好  别取笑我了
You got it, stop teasing me.
你刚才说的是"猪猪车"
Well, you said "Snatchy."
闭嘴  喝酒啦
Shut up, drink.
好
Okay.
电池电量剩余11分钟
11 minutes of battery life remaining.
他们到哪儿去了
Where are they?
外面越来越冷了
It's getting cold out here.
座圈加温
Warming seat.
不  保存体力
No, save your energy!
我自己用原始方法暖屁屁就好
I'll warm my butt the old-fashioned way.
终于来了
Finally.
你好呀  美人儿
Hello, what a beauty.
真是个妩媚妖娆的马桶
She's a hottie potty, baby, haw!
它能帮人擦屁股吗
Wow, does it wipe for you, too?
什么意思
What's wipe?
不尿白不尿啊
Now, I got to pee in this baby.
不行  别碰他  你这禽兽
No, get away from him, you monster!
他快死了
He's dying!
我们没时间了
We don't have much time!
给他冲点鸡汤下去
Flush some chicken soup into him!
-放一部他喜欢的电影  -对哦
- Or put on a movie he likes! - Yeah.
各位  请闭上眼为他祈祷
Everybody, close your eyes and believe.
不  我们得把他搬走
No, we have to move him.
起
Lift with your butts.
我去
Oh, man.
比我妈参加毕业舞会的时候还重
This is heavier than my mom at the prom.
她那时候正怀着我呢
'Cause she was pregnant with me.
电池剩余电量九分钟
Nine minutes of battery life remaining.
不不不不
Oh, no, no, no, no.
快  快  快走
Hurry, hurry... go!
驾  驾
Mush, mush!
休想冲走我
You can't flush me.
百福尔真不错  但我还是感觉有点饿
Wow, Beville's was great, but I'm still kind of hungry.
我也是  我们是不是忘记吃东西了
Me, too. Did we forget to eat?
天哪  真的
Oh, my God, we did.
谁管它呢
Who cares?
我们自己亲热吧
Let's just make out.
走观光路线吗  先生
Uh, scenic route, sir?
那还用说
You betcha.
坚持住  兄弟  就快到了
Hang in there, buddy, we're almost there.
用灵魂去蹬
Pedal with your heart!
是马克思・崇马彤
Ah, it's Max Flush!
-蹬快点  -走那边
- Pedal faster! - That way!
看不见他了
I don't see him.
好耶
Yeah!
我们做到了  我们做到了
We're doing it, we're doing it!
我们胜利在望了
Whoo-hoo, we're home free!
断桥
等等  前面没桥了  停
Wait, there's no bridge. Stop!
飞吧  马桶  飞吧
Fly, toilet, fly!
马桶不会飞  吉恩
Toilets can't fly, Gene.
这个马桶会
This one can!
激活桶翼
Activate wings!
播放翅膀乐队歌曲
Playing artist Wings.
由保罗・麦卡特尼于1971年组建的乐队
不不不不
N-n-n-n-no.
不
No...!
要想带走这马桶  得先过我这关
If you want this toilet, you'll have to go through me,
-马克思・崇马彤  -吉恩
- Max Flush! - Gene?
老爸  老妈
Dad? Mom?
你跟一个马桶在大马路上做什么
What you doing in the middle of the road with a toilet?
他不是简单的马桶
He's more than a toilet!
他是我最好的朋友  但他快死了
He's my best friend and he's dying!
-好吧  -他开始流血了
- Okay. - Ah, now he's losing fluids!
等下  这就是失踪的一万四的马桶吗
W-wait, is this that guy's missing $14,000 toilet?
我们必须马上给他充电
We need to get him to a power source immediately.
我觉得出租车司机不会同意
Well, I-I don't think we can ask the cab driver to...
-马桶要放车里吗  先生  -可以吗
- Toilet in the taxi, sir? - Really?
我还是没明白发生什么事了
I still don't really understand what's happening.
我也不明白  但我嗨着呢
I don't either, but I'm having fun.
那边有个咖啡店  咖啡店有接口的
There's a coffee shop... they'll have outlets.
那是给写剧本的人用的
For people writing screenplays.
停车
Pull over!
我醉了
I'm drunk.
电池剩余电量两分钟
Two minutes of battery life remaining.
那东西不能搬进店里
Hey, you can't bring that in here.
你们的标示只写"洗手间仅供顾客使用"
Your sign says restrooms are for customers only,
没说顾客不能自带洗手间啊
not that customers can't bring in their own restrooms.
那洗手间是我的
That restroom is mine.
是你呀  马桶兄
Hey, toilet guy.
看  我儿子帮你找到马桶了
Look, my son found your toilet.
我绝不会还给你
And I'll never give him back!
你只会把他带到某个地方让人坐上面大便
You just want to take him somewhere where he'll get pooped on!
我决不允许那样的事发生
I'll never let that happen!
谁也不许伤害他
I'll never let anything bad happen to him ever!
电量耗尽  再见
Battery dead. Good-bye.
不
No...!
孩子  他只是个马桶
Kid, he's a toilet.
充上电他就活过来了
He'll be fine once he's recharged.
他的家人还等着他呢  很好的家人
There's a family waiting for him... A very nice family...
就让我带他走吧
so let me take him.
他是我的  休想带走我俩任何一个
He belongs with me, and you'll never be able to move both of us!
对  你要是没经过吉恩同意就把他
Yeah, if you think you're gonna get Gene off the toilet
从马桶上拽下来  我就有坏消息要说了
before he's ready, I've got some bad news for you.
他有一次错过了他的生日派对
He missed his birthday party once.
-我们还请了小丑  -只好送他过去
- We had a clown. - We had to send him in there.
把马桶给我
You give me that toilet!
出什么问题了
What's the problem here?
没问题  没问题
No problem, no problem.
这帮人把外面的马桶搬进店里
These people brought in
赖着不走了
an outside toilet and they refuse to leave.
没错  这你可能得处理处理
Yeah, you should probably deal with that.
那好像就是新闻里那个被盗的马桶啊
Hey, that looks like that toilet that was reported stolen.
我就知道你们认得出来的嘛
Welp, sure hope you figure that out.
-站住  -站那儿别动
- Freeze! - Stop right there.
抓住他
Get him!
好样的
Yeah!
他们带你去的地方可没马桶
Where you're going, they don't have any toilets.
好吧有是有  但是露天的  丢死人了
Well, they do, but it's out in the open and it's embarrassing.
暖屁屁
Warm my butt.
你一无是处  一无是处
You're useless, useless!
吉恩  别冲马桶嚷嚷了
Gene, stop yelling at the toilet.
它只知道坐那儿吃
It just sits there and takes it.
我知道那个高级马桶是你的朋友
I know that fancy toilet was your friend
你很喜欢他
and you liked him,
但他不是你的  他现在很可能是证物了
but he wasn't yours and he's probably evidence now.
他需要我照顾  老爸  我让他失望了
He needed me to take care of him, Dad, and I let him down.
好东西总是与我无关
I'll never get to have anything nice,
面粉是  马桶也是
like a bag of flour or a toilet.
吉恩  照顾人不是件容易的事
Look, Gene, it's not easy to take care of things.
有一次  我在带还是婴儿的你的时候
I mean, one time when you were a baby and I was watching you,
不小心让你吃了草  幸好你没死
you ate a fern, and you could have died, but you didn't.
我的意思是  你已经尽全力
My point is, you tried to take care of the toilet
照顾那个马桶了
and you did the best you could.
谁都只能做到这里了
That's all anyone can do.
也许吧
I guess.
抱歉我跟你吼了
Sorry I yelled at you.
蠢不是你的错
It's not your fault you're stupid.
吉恩  快来  你朋友上电视了
Gene, get in here! Your friend's on TV!
今早  这艘船上的
This morning, the ferry's
最重要乘客不是人  而是一个马桶
most important passenger isn't a person, it's a toilet.
是他
It's him!
这个价值一万四的马桶据称是被一个叫
This $14,000 toilet was allegedly stolen
蒂姆・琼斯的人  也就是马桶大盗劫走
by a Tim Jones aka the Bathroom Burglar.
他说他叫马克思・崇马彤啊
He said his name was Max Flush.
你还真的信了
And you believed that?
-没有  我  -对啊  不  啥
- No, I'm... - Yeah... no, wha... why...
这个皇家级的马桶将会被送回皇颅岛
Fittingly, this royal flusher is headed back
回到他的合法拥有人手中
to its rightful owner on King's Head Island.
奥尔森・贝纳从渡船码头发回的现场报道
Live from the ferry landing, I'm Olsen Benner.
老妈  去开车
Mom, get the car.
我要去找我的马桶
I have to go to the toilet.
你这么说让我起了一身鸡皮疙瘩
Ooh, I got chills when you said that.
-他在那儿  -快去  吉恩
- There he is. - Gene, go!
抱歉  小朋友  你不能靠近那个马桶
Whoa, whoa, whoa, sorry, kid, can't go near that toilet.
警官  能给他开个后门吗
Uh, Officer, can you cut him a break?
说来话长  他只是想跟他告个别
It's a long story, but he-he just wants to say good-bye.
听着有点怪  不过好吧  他有一分钟
Kind of weird, but, all right, sir, your kid's got one minute.
你好马桶  我知道你听不见  但我只
Hello, toilet. I know you can't hear me, but I just...
你好  吉恩
Hello, Gene.
马桶  他们给你充电了
Toilet, they charged you.
-要启动坐浴盆功能吗  -太好了
- Activate bidet? - Yes!
不  我不是这个意思
I-I mean, no.
我想现在总算有时间跟你告别了
I think I just have time to say good-bye.
再见  吉恩
Good-bye, Gene.
我  我爱你
I... I love you.
请重复指令
Please repeat command.
我爱你
I love you.
你要吐吗
You would like to vomit?
不  我爱你
No, I love you.
抬起座圈以供呕吐
Seat up for vomit.
不  我爱你
No, I love you.
-请吐  -我爱你
- Vomit now. - I love you.
-吐  -我爱你
- Vomit. - I love you!
请吐  请吐
Vomit now. Vomit now.
别说了
Stop saying that!
-请吐  -你个白痴
- Vomit now. - Damn fool!
这太难过了
Okay, this is just sad.
我懂
I know.
你这衣服跟我爸穿过的很像
Huh, that suit looks just like one my dad had.
这衣服不错吧  我很喜欢
Yeah, it's a nice one, huh? I love it.
让我看看标签
Yeah, let me see the label.
-我  -有我爸的名字
- Um, I... - There's my dad's name.
"专为保尔・麦吉尔订做"
"Tailored for Paul McGill."
这就怪了  他明明叫鲍勃・汉堡啊
That's weird... his name is Bob Burgers.
这是我爸的衣服  你哪儿来的
That's my dad's suit! Where'd you get it?
-殡仪馆  -啥
- A funeral home? - What?!
殡仪馆  筹办葬礼的地方
A funeral home. It's a home for funerals.
我永远不会忘记那个马桶
I'll never forget that toilet.
我永远不会忘记那套西服
I'll never forget that suit.
至少生日礼物还穿在身上嘛
At least you still got your birthday suit.
只是有点皱巴了
Yeah, too bad it's wrinkly.
我们把老爸送去干洗吧
Let's get Dad dry-cleaned.
不  我来熨平他
Nah, I'll press him.
*抱紧我  宝贝*
*Baby, hold on to me, oh, yeah*
*该来的就让它来吧*
*Whatever will be will be*
*未来我们一起见证*
*The future is ours to see, yeah, come on*
*抱紧我  宝贝*
*So, baby, hold on to me*
*抱紧*
*Hold it*
*想想吧  宝贝*
*Think about it, baby*
*我会带你走向巅峰*
*I'm gonna take you to the top*
*宝贝  抱着我  抱紧我*
*So, baby, hold on to me, hold on tight*
*该来的就让他来吧  未来...*
*Whatever will be will be, say it again, the future is...*